(Leonard:)So, Missy, what brings you
all the way from Texas?
Was it perhaps destiny?
I think it was destiny.
My friend's getting married at Disneyland.
(Howard:)Destiny, thy name is Anaheim.
(Missy:)And I had to drop off some papers
for Shelly to sign for my dad's estate.
The papers could've been mailed. Mom
sent you here to spy on me, didn't she?
(Missy:)I guess that's why
they call you a genius.
(Sheldon:)They call me a genius
because I'm a genius.
(Sheldon:)Tell Mom
that I currently weigh 165 pounds...
(Sheldon:)...and that I'm having
regular bowel movements.
(Sheldon:)Enjoy the wedding. Goodbye.
- Whoa, whoa.
If the wedding's not till tomorrow,
why don't you stay with us tonight?
(Missy:)Oh, I don't think so.
Shelly doesn't like company.
(Missy:)Even as a little boy, he'd send his imaginary
friends home at the end of the day.
(Sheldon:)They were not friends.
They were imaginary colleagues.
(Leonard:)Look, you're here,
and we have plenty of room.
- No, we don't.
- Come on, Shelly, she's family.